Episode 1
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure hidden at the end of the sea?
And anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the conscious point's our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets, every tear that we pride
only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
Oh crap, he's not holding back!
We gotta move!
Everything here is done for.
So that's where those detestable Shandora
warriors have hidden their village.
They're originally from the blue sea!
Surely they would love to go home.
Now, fall to the world below!
Our village! No!
It's been destroyed!
That could have been us.
If we had waited any
longer, we'd be ashes.
In the name of Great Warrior Kal 'gara!
Light the fire of Shandora!
Wiper!
Wiper, Great Warrior Kal 'gara,
your distant ancestor had many reasons
for wanting to take back our homeland,
but one you may not know he
had another reason yes it
would become his greatest
regret now listen great warrior
Kalgara had a very close friend
Kalgara had a friend that's
right he came to know Kalgara
400 years ago his name Mont
The following tale took place long,
long ago, some 400 years in the past.
And though it was never written down,
it has remained in people's hearts
from one generation to the next.
Get back to the ship, quick!
The monster of Century is right
behind us! Hurry! Cast off! Cast off!
But, Captain, there's still criminal.
Just get us out to sea!
Now you'll face my wrath!
Leave your possessions.
Flee with your lives.
Sir, the Daily Report.
I'm sorry to inform you that we've
reached the end of our food supply,
Meaning, of course, we are now
lost at sea and will slowly die.
The cook fainted. Damn it!
No more food!
Looks like the Commodore
fell into the sea.
This is the Grand Line.
Did he decide to drown himself
and leave us to our fates?
Maybe he decided on a quick
death over starvation.
Don't be stupid.
The Commodore is a great man.
He's already returned
twice from these waters.
Yeah, what are these carefully
folded clothes and shoes here for?
Hey, someone go check.
Screw that!
This sea is chock full of monsters.
He's not coming up.
Commodore!
He was a crafty one. Here.
Uh, what's the rope for?
Haul it in, boys.
Whoa, what is that thing?
Commodore, did you kill
that beast under water?
Cook it up for us.
I've been getting lazy.
Man, must be losing my touch.
This storm's a real Wapol, Commodore.
Ah, I've been through worse.
What?
How does that help us?
The yardarm's been broken off. Where?
Made, made.
This third voyage has kept
us at sea for over two years.
And it's a miracle we've lasted this long.
Hey, did anybody else hear that?
Hear what you mean the thunder no it's
something else something
beautiful like a bell
Priest are you certain of
this this land is cursed
at this rate the shendorians
will be wiped out
Then what can we do to
save the village priest we
must offer another girl
at the sacrificial altar
Too much death how many now
Well over a hundred how can this be
nothing like this has ever happened to us
If i can help save the village then
i will gladly sacrifice my life
Why do you cry, Mother?
It is truly an honor to be chosen as
sacrifice and embraced by the sun god.
Today is a proud and happy day for
me, and it should be for you as well.
Thank you so much for raising
me right these many years, Mama.
If this is a bad dream, let me wake up!
Get off of me!
Get off!
Go away!
Great warrior Kalgara.
Stella.
I wanted to grow up to
be just like you someday.
I wanted to be a brave warrior
and fight to protect this land.
I don't want to die from
something like this.
You're amazing, Commodore.
We took the heading you said to,
and sure enough, there's an island.
Yes, how fortunate.
We can ride out the storm here.
Still, you sure none of you guys heard it?
Nope, none of us heard any
bells. Isn't that right?
Yeah, you must have been
hearing things, Commodore.
That's quite a forest.
I hope we find stuff to help our research.
Drop, drop, drop.
Hey, Commodore, there's your bell.
All right, enough, boys.
No need to tease.
Do you really think I'd mistake
that freak bird call for a bell?
Wait, Commodore, did you...
It's unreal.
It has such a beautiful tone.
Seems there are people here after all.
Hey, Commodore, slow down. Wait for us.
Someone's collapsed over here.
Intruders.
Hey, you there.
Commodore.
He doesn't look right.
Get back here!
Let me go!
It's a plague called tree fever.
From the looks of him,
he hasn't been treated.
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
Doctor, check our Cannon stores.
Administer doses to this young
man and the crew immediately.
This is terrible.
Even the crops are being eaten away.
Commodore, the whole village is infected!
Bring the girl to the altar!
God of the sun!
God of the rain!
God of the forest, God of the earth,
in exchange for this girl's life,
we beseech you, spare our village.
It's the Kashi God.
For the village, let her go.
The Kashi god, such a divine former!
Please save my mother.
Please save my son and spare my father.
What's that?
Something fell in? Fell in?
What just happened? Who is that?
Kashi, no!
He's killed a god!
The ceremony is over.
You must have been frightened.
But you're safe now.
Now, there's no need to die.
Kashi!
Please forgive us!
We're going to be killed both!
Offer the gods more lives!
Before we incur their wrath!
Kill them!
The Commodore's gone
and done it this time.
They sound really bad.
Guy just can't keep to himself.
He killed a god?
What does that mean?
Tribal rituals ain't something
you mess around with.
Well, the gods ain't a
great warrior, Kalgara.
I am an explorer from the North
Blue, Commodore Montplotor.
I don't care who you are, outsider.
You must be eliminated.
Eliminated?
Is that your answer?
You just destroy old manor of progress?
You have no right to impose your values.
Now say goodbye.
Who is this guy?
He's holding his own against Kalgara.
Girl, use that blade to
give your life to the gods!
Do what?
A sacrifice meant to save the entire
village, weeping because she wants to live?
Disgraceful!
Don't be a fool!
Stop!
Commodore, no!
For centuries,
our people have strictly
upheld the sacred commandment
that all intruders on this
island must be punished.
And you have committed the
unforgivable sin of slaughtering Kashi.
You alone cannot atone for that.
You and all your men
will pay with your lives.
Sacrifices this lives
that it's insane how does!
That make your gods happy?
These ceremonies are flat-out denials of
the triumphs of all great men before us.
I won't stand for it.
You insult every adventurer
and researcher who's ever
set out to see in hopes of
bringing prosperity to mankind.
How shameful if your
gods value your lives?
wouldn't they have contempt
for these very ceremonies?
Give me some time, people.
Your so-called curse, I
will lift it for good.
And if I cannot, you may do what
you will with my crew and I.
What nonsense!
Do you think you're a god?
and in return if i do save this village
from tragedy you must
swear never to perform
this ceremony again is
that all you have to
say ridiculous now
prepare to die let him try
what do you say chief
no you will have until
sundown tomorrow when your crew will die
I accept your terms.
Oh.
Well, fellas, come sunset tomorrow,
looks like it's goodbye world for us.
Have faith in the Commodore.
Hey, pretty lady, I feel bad for you, too.
It's a shame you were born here.
Yeah, with your looks, you could have married
an aristocrat and lived the good life.
Knock it off, guys.
Learn a little tact.
Who is he?
Huh? Who?
You mean the Commodore?
His name is Montblanc Noland.
He's a rather famous explorer.
He's also a skilled botanist.
He explores uncharted islands and documents
new species of plants for his research.
He's pretty much a hero in our country.
But he's way too nice a guy.
Yeah, it's impossible for him
to ignore a situation like this.
We know we can trust him, though!
Why did you not let Kalgara
kill him right then?
The answer will make
itself known tomorrow.
He says he can save our village.
There is no harm in waiting.
How can you be so sure?
You'll listen to him, but
not the shaman's dying words?
Kalgara, please say
something about this outrage.
If I sense that the village is
in even the slightest danger,
I will not hesitate to take that
man's head before sunset tomorrow.
I may not have the power to
hear the words of the gods.
However, I can hear the words
of a man who speaks in earnest.
Now that is all.
What are you still doing awake?
I'm all better.
Great warrior Kal 'gara?
What did he mean by progress?
Here we are.
A Conney tree.
I knew there had to be one.
In a forest this huge?
Earthquake!
It's here!
Kashi's wrath has finally come!
Let us out of here, please!
Such devastation.
The forest floor has sunk.
It looks as if the island
is tearing itself apart.
You're looking well I
suppose the gods have
taken your punishment into
their own divine hands.
Then your gods have grown weak they lack
the strength to kill
even one lowly explorer.
Stubborn fool sorry but would you mind
leaving I don't feel like looking at you.
I have to hurry to the village how amusing
I'll enjoy watching this
go ahead and squirm.
Another warrior has died there
is that terrible earthquake.
You are the evil spirits
now we will punish you
this wasn't the agreement
look out stop stop.
Seto muicide what's the meaning of
this this is pathetic the Shandora
warriors I know and look up to they
show a lot more pride than you do
kid it won't be long now you should
prepare yourself for when the sun
sets that's when the lives of your
men will be an offering unto the gods.
Damn it!
My, the Earth certainly did
swallow you up skillfully.
It was truly an act of God.
The fact that you're still alive
is what's hardest to believe.
The ground.
Prepare for the ceremony!
Bring every sacrifice to the altar!
Please, wait a little longer.
The Commodore will be
back in a few more hours.
Give us more time, please!
Why are they doing this to us?
The Sun is setting the
ceremony must be starting soon
How disgusting is this the wreck
of a man who defied the gods?
What exactly are you so afraid of?
Afraid you fear what you
do not know and you trade
innocent people's lives
for false consolations.
What are you saying?
Sacrifices are pointless deaths.
We have lived this way for centuries.
That doesn't make it right.
Silence.
You don't know what you're talking about.
The lives of your citizens
are more precious than gods.
They're real people.
Take the sacrifices to the altar!
Burn them at the stake and
send them to the heavens!
Commodore, don't let them burn us!
You can send an innocent
girl to her death.
And have no remorse, so
I doubt you'd understand.
But try.
What you're doing is less than human.
Don't you see that?
No remorse, you say.
The innocent girl you speak of.
She was my daughter!
What?
You would tell your own
daughter to give up her life?
You're very wrong, and
you don't understand.
Stand, there is so much power in the words
of our gods, and the people must obey.
The gods will not hear our pleas, even
if we ask them to spare our children.
It's smaller than the last one.
It must be one of Kashi's children.
The god's blood has come
to pass judgment on you.
Judgment, my ass.
Let me explain tree fever is a plague
a plague that wiped out hundreds
of thousands of lives In my own village
years ago and now it is ravaging
yours but it's gone no one's died
in decades as a Result of this awful
disease no one and do you know why
because we discovered a cure for it
I'm holding in my hand
bark from the Conney tree
This is the cure I only need to
extract the Conney from it If I
can bring this back to your people
I can save all of their lives
But you insist on keeping countless
masses from their cure Do you
realize how many innocent victims
have already perished because of you?
So I stand by what I said Your
ceremonies are an insult to my people.
You're too busy blindly
trampling over great
advancements to see how
much it could benefit you.
I may die in judgment, or
I may die in an accident.
At least I'll stay true to my people.
How will your village die?
By ignorance?
Is the pain you cause your people
worth it to be true to your gods?
I can hear the words of a
man who speaks in earnest.
Answer this?
What is this thing?
What have I killed?
A snake.
No, you're wrong!
I just broke one of our commandments.
I just killed a precious god.
A god!
Do you understand me?
But all you can see is a snake!
And you see our deadly curse
as some curable disease!
Tell me, can you save our village?
I can.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
When you're lost and alone,
I can always hear your voice.
While you wander far from
home, gazing up at the sky.
You are just like the moon,
you never change as you
climb into the night.
But your reflection waves.
Then you disappear, fading so silently.
Stay as you are, don't lose your way.
Let these words guide you.
Don't ever look back.
Don't give up on your dreams.
They're windless nights.
They come to you.
All again and again.
Until you see the journey through.
You may not pretend.
I hope that you'll learn.
To put your past behind.
And just keep moving on.